{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40131/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40131,"taskName":"Kitchen - Remodel","taskDescription":"Remodel a Kitchen","xmTaskDescriptor":"Kitchen Remodelers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":139,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"kitchen remodel design sinks countertops","textMessagingName":"Remodel Kitchen","rolloverLongDesc":"This is for major changes, not just replacing an appliance, floor or redecorating. For less comprehensive changes, check under the specific category such as plumbing, tile installation or painting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Add a kitchen or substantially alter an old one.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel a Kitchen.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Kitchen Remodeling \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen Renovation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Kitchen Remodel","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Kitchen - Remodel","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Kitchen Remodeling Project","urlName":"Kitchen-Remodel","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Kitchen Remodeling Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"kitchen,remodel,design,sinks,countertops,cabinets,appliances,island,pantry,cupboards,granite,flooring,lighting,remodeling,remodelers,convert, general, contractor, renovation","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":442,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"taskHeader":"Kitchen Remodelers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40131/":{"taskOID":40131,"originalTaskOID":40131,"setID":442,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7566,"questionDisplayText":"Floorplan","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Floorplan","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11481,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I plan to maintain existing kitchen floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I plan to maintain existing kitchen floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11482,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am considering changes to kitchen floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I am considering changes to kitchen floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7567,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinets","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Cabinets","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11483,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to move or update the cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to move or update the cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the cabinets","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7568,"questionDisplayText":"Appliances","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Appliances","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11485,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to move or update some or all appliances","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to move or update some or all appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the appliances","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7569,"questionDisplayText":"Countertops","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Countertops","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11487,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11488,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7570,"questionDisplayText":"Sinks","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Sinks","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11489,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11490,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7571,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Flooring","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11491,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11492,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7572,"questionDisplayText":"Lighting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Lighting","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11493,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11494,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7566,"questionDisplayText":"Floorplan","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Floorplan","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11481,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I plan to maintain existing kitchen floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I plan to maintain existing kitchen floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11482,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am considering changes to kitchen floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I am considering changes to kitchen floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11481,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I plan to maintain existing kitchen floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I plan to maintain existing kitchen floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11482,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am considering changes to kitchen floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I am considering changes to kitchen floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7567,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinets","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Cabinets","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11483,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to move or update the cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to move or update the cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the cabinets","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11483,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to move or update the cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to move or update the cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the cabinets","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7568,"questionDisplayText":"Appliances","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Appliances","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11485,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to move or update some or all appliances","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to move or update some or all appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the appliances","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11485,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to move or update some or all appliances","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to move or update some or all appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the appliances","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to move or update the appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7569,"questionDisplayText":"Countertops","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Countertops","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11487,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11488,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11487,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11488,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7570,"questionDisplayText":"Sinks","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Sinks","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11489,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11490,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11489,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11490,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7571,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Flooring","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11491,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11492,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11491,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11492,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7572,"questionDisplayText":"Lighting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Lighting","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11493,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11494,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11493,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11494,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}